hebeos.co.uk 2018-08-31

# Privacy Policy at Hebeos

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website?**

When ordering or registering on our site as intended, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience with your purchase.

**Use of information**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

To personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

To improve user experience on our website in order to better serve you.

To allow us to better service you.

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

To quickly process your transactions.

**Data Protection Policy**

We are fully PCI compliant to the industries highest standards. Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

We use regular Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information. All transactions are for security purposes processed through a banking provider and are not stored on our servers.

**Cookie Policy**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

Cookies power the:

Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.

Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.

Keep track of advertisements.

Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

By visiting our site, third party services such as Facebook, Google, Twitter, Livechatinc, or Adroll may place cookies into your browser on our behalf to make the users experience better and for advertising or targeted advertising purposes.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled but it won't affect the users’ experience. You can still place orders.

**Third Party Disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise, transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information such as IP Address, cookie identifiers and your website activity may be collected by other parties for marketing, advertising, targeted advertising or other uses when using our website. You can always opt-out by visiting the EDAA opt-out site at youronlinechoices.eu or the DAA opt-out site www.aboutads.info or the NAI opt-out site at networkadvertising.org/choices.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
